[Music]
thank you
that's all the [__] we don't want
finally out of the house are you ready
to open up shop
definitely do you think anyone will stop
by our lemonade standpros
nope
we need to do something to convince
people to come to our yard sale instead
of the one across the street
on second thought first I want you to
take some money across the street and
buy something from that nice lady over
there
why she's been looking over at us all
day I think she noticed that our yard
sale is so much bigger than hers and now
she's too embarrassed to say anything
you can leave it to us mama
it's our mission to bring smiles and joy
to everyone
hey you're the kids of
decided to have yard sale on the same
day as me manic have you kissed your
brother on the lips today
no why the [__] would I do that
no reason I'm sorry I don't have much
merchandise my husband is bedridden with
cancer and about to die
but every little bit helps
play useless cow did you finish scamming
them for money yet we still haven't paid
off the Pay-Per-View channels for our
Roku TV
honey get back inside how long is this
going to take you told me to pretend
that I have cancer
now all my friends think I'm weak
I'm tired of watching we're runs of Deal
or No Deal why don't you ever listen to
a thing I say [__] look at you you look
like Manic the Hedgehog Sonic
Underground is [__] dead come
unbanned let's go
where are you going
we're going home there is no business to
be done here
no you're not you're going to buy my
wife's [__]
Daniel please just go inside what did
you call me you know illegally changed
my name to Sonic Sonic just go inside
no everyone else calls me Sonic
you call me bro bro go inside
one more mistake like that and you've
got yourself a one-way ticket out of the
manic X Sonic fan club
I'm going inside to wait for you to come
suck my fat nuts
[Music]
oh
Savory sausage and gravy what is my
[__] doing holding a yard sale on a
Saturday morning he should be spending
the day inside having fun
I the richest man alive better go make
him stop before someone makes fun of him
for looking poor
hey Sonic look at your boyfriend Bartle
P Montclair of Dresden maybe he wants to
buy some lemonade
babe wait it's not what it looks like
you [__] ever since we started dating
you told me you were among the top eight
of the most richest people on Earth and
that you don't travel anywhere with
anything less than twelve thousand
dollars I would like you to empty your
pockets and place your belongings on the
table
let's go [__] quit stalling if you are
not lying you should be eager for the
chance to prove it
there two sent Sanders to cup Double Gum
are you happy
no [__] I am not happy but I am
relieved that you came clean it takes a
big man with a big tissue to admit when
they're poor
now then with the cover
don't spank me no listen sugar balls
please Bartleby don't do it I already
apologized
no you have been a very naughty boy
today naughty boys need a smack on the
honey I don't want it show me that dirty
unwiped [__] or I shall fetch a
wooden spoon and use it upon you until
you obey you are getting a spanking and
debt final okay
use your words Lord boy
I understand
thank you Sonic you did a terribly
naughty thing today but you already knew
that
I'm sorry everyone yes I'm sure you're
sorry now that you're here in front of
us about to have your ass smacked
take it away Mr Montclair I have grown
tired of waiting
foreign
damn I'm hungry I could sure go for him
a cake right about now
hey I'm at the computer I'll just see if
there's an easy recipe online
oh hell yeah that's what daddy wants
after I created my chocolate mug cake
recipe I realized that nothing beats a
cake you can't rep in one minute
obviously Karen that's why I'm here
oh man that picture looks so good will
might be like that it better not have
those rainbow sprinkles I'm no brussy
little [__] vanilla milk cake some
people may think him exaggerating when I
say that mug cake changed my life oh not
this again no one needs to hear your
life story [__]
what the hell is this oh I'm okay
if I was on a diet would I even be
looking up cakes at all
oh my God that mug cake that's the same
one as before
wait this one has a spoon in it actually
hold it for cup
you son of a [__]
Knuckles my grandson it is going on 12.
so I am going to leave this homemade
pineapple upside down cake
outside your bedroom door when you find
yourself hungry please eat it and tell
me how it tastes
please give me the social interaction in
which you have denied me for days
[__] off old man your food tastes like
butt crack
why don't you fetch me some actual good
food like spicy chicken fries from BK
laughs
[Music]
look big bro it's a superhero he's come
to save us from our abusive household
play you old fart did you notice that
you just passed and in my little
sister's face
did you notice that I don't give a [__]
perhaps your sister wanted to take a
great big whiff of the Great Sage of the
Echidna smelly gas have you ever thought
of that no
well what are you going to do about it I
am going to stand here and judge you
very very harshly
the pleasure is mine elderly friend
may I ask what sort of words are you
selling preferably something to earn the
love and admiration of rebellious
Echidna boy
please help recondult the relationship
of a Kind old man and his great-grandson
you mean the one and only big booty
Sonic
oh you hedgehogs you don't know how much
this means to me
um okay
I mean it your boy is over there with no
adults Insight you did more for me than
you could even believe thank you for
this once in a lifetime opportunity
I don't know what kind of [__] you're
planning here but you better cut it out
real fast or else I'll put you guys back
on a floating island against Joel again
but I don't want to sell my collection
of Twilight dolls
believe me [__] sister the bluebler
here's your plea I also do not fancy
much having to punt off my Jacob Black
doll but we have to make ends meet if we
are going to continue funding
our dear brother Mannix anger management
studies
hey Sonic is your boyfriend Bartleby
close by to protect you
not right no no why
[Music]
thank you
London Ramirez and crafts
[Music]
a yard sale I better find some
right here look Indian food
it's not alien food they're arts and
craft beans and why the hell do they
appear to be eight [__] whole dollars
what kind of store do they think they're
running here
are still running they can be expensive
crafts like ones you can find for 389
dollars at the Hobby Lobby
perhaps what do you think are earthlings
slave
is that supposed to be a friendship
bracelet it's not even measured
correctly it's like 20 inches around oh
it's 20 inches that's sometimes like
chunky balls put the [__] background
Nick
I'm just going to buy those fuzzy
looking red socks to wear out of my
smelly green feet
these thoughts were definitely worn on
the soles of the ball being Prince Sonic
the Hedgehog let's find in addition to
my collection the fella won't be a
builder I demand to purchase your new
face there are funny stockings
[Music]
diamonds in excellent condition
foreign
[Music]
Bobby you can't don't listen to those
demons of the Fowler's Darkness puppy
taking your life is never the answer
yes there is still so much to live for
[Music]
though you see I told you ain't no one
gives no damn about your friendship
bracelet
[Applause]
your manic's uncle have you seen my
great Granddad anywhere he was supposed
to bring back Burger King chicken fries
but I think he got scared and ran away
again
child make sure he doesn't steal
anything while he's here
no way is this manix PS2 why on Earth
would he be giving this away
Knuckles Knuckles Knuckles my favorite
no good son of a [__] I take it you
came to check out our garage sale with
your grabs
but hey manic didn't expect to see you
here you dumbass this is my house hi is
that my PS2
[__] I told Mama not to bring it out
here thanks for watching out for me
Nooks you're a real one
actually it's mine
you are a phony and a deceiver I've been
to your house every day this summer
you don't even own a PlayStation well
now I'm embarrassed here I wanted to
surprise a friend on a sunny afternoon
to play the hit game Bakugan Battle
Brawlers for the PlayStation 2. but
apparently I can't even do that
oh my are we talking about batch again
over here I just laughed back chicken
almost as much as Taco Bell Cinnabon
Delights because they too are shaped
like balls
give me back my shit's knuckles I would
hate to throw down with your ass in
front of my girlfriend
used old things oh no cause I thought so
much better review everyone knows
stealing is wrong how do you think I
would feel if someone stole the clothes
right off my back
maybe leave it to the professionals so
you don't get caught like a [__]
how
Sonia what is the matter it's at there
he used his magic to trap us in a bubble
he's being very sexually aggressive
right now but only towards Sonic he's
just ignoring me as if I'm ugly or
something
yeah that happens a lot
everyone back the [__] up I'll get
through that barrier if it's the last
thing I do
no that sexy hunk may be your
grandfather but it's my best friend who
is trapped in there
[Music]
and she needs my help it is time for
this love to prove her worth
[Music]
how did you manage to shatter my barrier
one would need the force of at least 10
nuclear bombs to make so much as it end
rumors don't do me just this old man I'm
all charged up on Starbucks pink Drink
and I am ready to go
[Music]
[Applause]
you'll never be able to defeat me
one-on-one salty girl
these spells were specifically designed
to be used against horse
[Music]
thank you what the [__]
goodness gracious unless my eyes there's
anything that was a magic block from the
ancient saint of the actions I'll have
to intervene at the random being
here we are good things I often carry
around the legendary golden Buddhist
resident its car is enormous but
sometimes people need that foot at the
edge
[Music]
foreign
is this the power of cosmetic procedures
[Music]
you did it Mindy you saved me
of course girlfriend
I think someone earned themselves a hug
weathering it in home girl just don't
hug too tight so you don't pop my boobs
why do you always have to embarrass me
Granddad did you seriously have to try
and rape Sonic for the 14th time this
weekend now he might not even invite us
over for whipped cream and pumpkin pie
anymore
what I didn't try to rape anybody
then what was that about you going on
for my bro's cheeks
Sonic my boy you're making me look like
a [__] [__]
please turn around and take
responsibility for your actions
foreign
my favorite
as you can plainly see now I was never
going to harm the poor lad the truth is
I stopped by the gas station to buy a
bag of chips to surprise my cute red
great grandson but as luck may have it
Sonic sat upon them with his ginormous
ass and they were trapped in those
[__] cheeks
when I informed him of the situation he
called me gay [__] is this true did you
steal his corn chips after I went pee
I only wanted yummy chips he's the one
acting like a baby
hey son ex-mum how much is his Twilight
doll collection
35 cents
then I'll buy it so that he can't have
it
in fact I'll go the mile and buy
everything here for three dollars
[Applause]
[Music]
tonight
I don't tell myself
[Music]
to where we started
and fights
[Music]
painkillers